Register of the Atlantic Council of the United States Records, 1950-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- ATLANTIC CONGRESS, LONDON, JUNE 1959
  - Netherlands National Committee
    - "Technical and Economic Assistance to Underdeveloped Countries Members of NATO" (Folder 7)
  - "The Next Ten Years" (Folder 8)
  - News releases
    - General (Folder 9)
    - New York (Folder 10)
    - Washington, D.C. (Folder 11)
    - Women (Folder 12)
  - Nuveen, John, "A Coordinated Cold War Offensive" (Folder 13)
  - Official guests and observers (Folder 14)
  - Olver, A. S. B., "Western Interests in Independent Non-Communist Eastern and Southern Asia" (Folder 15)
  - Opening ceremony by Her Majesty the Queen, June 5, 1959 (Folder 16)
  - Organization of (Folder 17)
  - Organizational chart (Folder 18)
  - Orgill, Edmund (Folder 19)
  - Papi, Ugo, "Economic Development of the Atlantic Community Countries" (Folder 20)
  - Pelleri, Paolo, "Freedom of Trade and Stability of Exchange Rates" (Folder 21)
  - Pierson, M. A., "East-West Relations" (Folder 22)
  - Points and suggestions (Folder 23)
  - Political Committee Report (Folder 24)
  - Porte, Della, "Economic Integration and Western Europe" (305, Folder 1)
  - Press clippings (Folder 2-6)
  - Press clippings (306, Folder 1-3)
  - Press mailing lists (Folder 4)
  - Press releases
    - General (Folder 5)
    - First meetings of Main Committees, June 6 (Folder 6)
    - Monday Plenary Session, June 8 (Folder 7)
    - Special Plenary Session, June 9 (Folder 8)
    - Tuesday Plenary Session (II), June 9 (Folder 9)
  - Publicity (Folder 10)
  - Resolution (Folder 11)
  - Rhyne, Charles S., "A Background Paper on the 'Rule of Law'" (Folder 12)
  - Rowan, Leslie
    - "Economic Policy (General)" (Folder 13)
    - "Trade and Currency Problems" (Folder 14)
  - Seton-Watson, Professor, "Soviet and Western Propaganda" (Folder 15)
  - Speeches
    - Fens, J. J. (Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Mordecai (Folder 17)
    - Kefauver, Estes (Folder 18)
    - Lange, Minister (Folder 19)
    - Oldenbroek, J. (Folder 20)
    - President's closing speech (Folder 21)
    - Queen at opening (Folder 22)
    - Saceur (Folder 23)
    - Spaak, Paul-Henri (Folder 24)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert (Folder 25)
    - Wright, Jerauld (307, Folder 1)
  - Streit, Clarence, "Ten Advantages of Proposed Atlantic Convention Method" (Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee reports (Folder 3)
  - Suggestions for proposals (Folder 4)
  - Summary of the discussions, recommendations and resolutions of the committees of the Atlantic Congress (Folder 5)
  - Thistlewaite, Frank, "An Atlantic Institute" (Folder 6)
  - U.S. Committee for the Atlantic Congress
    - General (Folder 7-9)
    - Airlines (Folder 10)
    - American Council on NATO, Inc. (Folder 11)
    - Atlantic Institute (Folder 12)
    - Audit report and financial statements (Folder 13)
    - Bank statements (Folder 14)
    - Berlin (Folder 15)
    - Board members (Folder 16-17)
    - By-laws (Folder 18)
    - Chairmen, rapporteurs, speakers and participants (Folder 19)
    - Contributors (Folder 20)
    - Correspondence
      - General (308, Folder 1)
      - Douglas, Lewis (Folder 2)
      - Dulles, John Foster (Folder 3)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Folder 4)
      - Johnson, Eric (Folder 5)
      - Macomber, William B. (Folder 6)
      - Merchant, Livingston T. (Folder 7)
      - Nixon, Richard (Folder 8)
      - Robinson, Douglas (Folder 9)
      - U.S. Congress (Folder 10)
      - Wallace, Richard (Folder 11-12)
    - Delegates, regrets (Folder 12A-12B)
    - District of Columbia, income tax withheld (Folder 13)
    - Employer's tax, income tax withheld, FICA (Folder 14)
    - Employer's quarterly federal tax return (Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee meetings (Folder 16)
    - Expenses (309, Folder 1-2)
    - Finances (Folder 3)
    - Financial statements (Folder 4)
    - Forms, memoranda, etc. (Folder 5)
    - Foundations and grants (Folder 6)
    - Invitatations (Folder 7-8)
    - Meetings
      - 1958 December 9 (310, Folder 1)
      - 1959
        - January 8 (Folder 2)
        - January 30 (Folder 3)
        - April 13 (Folder 4)
        - May 25 (Folder 5)
    - NATO Parliamentarian's Conference, November 1958 (Folder 6)
    - Office set-up (Folder 7)
    - Organizational papers (Folder 8)
    - Payroll (Folder 9)
    - Personnel (Folder 10)
    - Petty cash receipts (Folder 11)
    - Publicity (Folder 12-13)
    - Replies to letters requesting contributions (311, Folder 1-3)
    - Requests for information (Folder 4)
    - Rhyne, Charles (Folder 5)
    - Schmidt, Adolph W. (Folder 6)
    - Selection Committee meetings, 1959
      - January 29 (Folder 7)
      - April 1 (Folder 8)
    - Senate Concurrent Resolution 17 (Folder 9)
    - Stationery (Folder 10)
    - Tax exemptions (Folder 11)
    - Telegrams (312, Folder 1)
    - Wallygrams (Folder 2)
  - U.S. Delegation
    - Committee C-3, Western European Integration (Folder 3)
    - "The U.S.S.R. and NATO" (Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of State, press release, "Western Peace Plan,", May 14, 1959 (Folder 5)
  - U.S. President's messages pertaining to NATO (Folder 6)
  - "United States Press Comments on the Atlantic Congress" (Folder 7)
  - Van Zeeland, Paul, "NATO and the Smaller States" (Folder 8)
  - White, Morton B., "The NATO Information Program" (Folder 9)
- ATLANTIC INSTITUTE, 1959-1978
  - 1959-1960 (312, Folder 10-11)
  - 1960 (Folder 12)
  - 1960 (313, Folder 1)
  - 1960-61 (Folder 2)
  - 1961 (Folder 3-8)
  - 1961 (314, Folder 1-7)
  - 1962 (315, Folder 1)
  - 1967 (Folder 2)
  - 1968-69 (Folder 3)
  - 1969 (Folder 4-6)
  - 1969-1970 (Folder 7)
  - 1970 (316, Folder 1)
  - 1971 (Folder 2)
  - 1972 (Folder 3)
  - 1973 (Folder 4)
  - 1973-74 (Folder 5)
  - 1975 (Folder 6)
  - 1976 (Folder 7)
  - 1978 (Folder 8)
  - General (317, Folder 1)
  - Ackley, Gardner
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Checking copies of writings (Folder 3)
    - Lists of persons studies sent to (Folder 4)
    - Orders for studies by, 1971-72 (Folder 5-6)
    - Press clippings (Folder 7-8)
  - ACUS loan to AI, 1969 (Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board, minutes of meetings, 1970 (318, Folder 1)
  - AI governors and sponsors, 1963-67 (Folder 2)
  - Aid to Education Project
    - General (Folder 3-4)
    - Mailing list (Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Assembly, 1964-65 (Folder 6-8)
  - Atlantic economic relations with the developing nations, including coordination of aid and trade policies (Folder 9)
  - Audit, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Audited statement, 1964 (Folder 11)
  - Auditor's Report, April 1966 (Folder 12)
  - Auditor's reports and annual financial reports, 1961-65 (Folder 13)
  - Background and by-laws (319, Folder 1)
  - Bank statements
    - 1968 (Folder 2)
    - Paris First National City Bank, 1964 (Folder 3)
    - Special account, 1963-64 (Folder 4)
  - Bills, 1971 (Folder 5-6)
  - Board of Governors
    - 1962 (Folder 7)
    - 1967-68 (Folder 8)
    - Committee members, 1965-67 (Folder 9)
    - Members, 1966 (Folder 10)
    - Memoranda for, 1962 (Folder 11)
    - Memoranda and notes, 1963-64 (Folder 12)
    - Minutes of meetings
      - 1962 (Folder 13)
      - 1963 (Folder 14)
  - Budget, proposed, 1964 (Folder 15)
  - Camu, Louis, "The Dollar Crisis and Europe"
    - General (Folder 16)
    - Draft manuscripts (320, Folder 1)
    - Orders, 1971-72 (Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1971-72 (Folder 3)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations (Folder 4)
  - Clippings (Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Middle East Institute (Folder 6-8)
  - Conference on Capital Markets, Cannes, January 19-22, 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Conference on Strategies for the Atlantic Technological Development, Rome, May 24-26, 1968
    - Conclusions and recommendations (Folder 10)
    - "The Myth and Challenge of the Technological Gap" (Folder 11)
  - Conferences
    - General (Folder 12)
    - The Atlantic Community and the Third World, Autumn, 1969 (Folder 13)
    - Declaration of "Long-Range Aims" of the Atlantic Community, Paris, May 24-25, 1962 (Folder 14)
    - Young Leaders Conference, Bergneustadt, May 15-17, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Contributions
    - 1962 (Folder 16)
    - 1964 January-June (Folder 17)
  - Contributors (Folder 18)
  - Correspondence
    - 1963 (321, Folder 1)
    - 1963-64 (Folder 2-3)
    - 1964-65 (Folder 4)
    - 1967 (Folder 5)
    - 1970 (Folder 6)
    - Acheson, Dean, 1964 (Folder 7)
    - Achilles, Theodore C., 1964-68 (Folder 8-9)
    - Badoux, Jean Claude, 1964-65 (Folder 10)
    - Benoit, Leroy, 1964 (Folder 11)
    - Biller, Joel, 1964 (Folder 12)
    - Birrenbach, Kurt, 1964-65 (Folder 13)
    - Boehm, Eric, 1964 (Folder 14)
    - Borcier, Paul, 1963-65 (Folder 15)
    - Bowie, Robert, 1963-65 (Folder 16)
    - Brewster, Beverly, 1967 (Folder 17)
    - Brundage, Percival, 1964-65 (Folder 18)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1964 (Folder 19)
    - Burden, William, 1964-65 (Folder 20)
    - Cerych, Ladislav, 1964-65 (Folder 21)
    - Chrisney, Judson C., 1965 (Folder 22)
    - Clayton, William L., 1964-65 (Folder 23)
    - Darden, Colgate, 1964-65 (Folder 24)
    - Deshormes, Philippe, 1966-67 (Folder 25)
    - Elliott, William Y., 1963 (Folder 26)
    - Eppstein, John, 1964-65 (Folder 27)
    - Ferber, Daniel A., 1967-68 (Folder 28)
    - Fichera, M. (Olivetti Company), 1964 (Folder 29)
    - Franklin, George S., 1964 (Folder 30)
    - Garwood, Ellen, 1964-66 (Folder 31)
    - George, James, 1965 (Folder 32)
    - Hahn, Kurt, 1965 (Folder 33)
    - Holmes, John W., 1964 (Folder 34)
    - Hovey, J. Allan, 1964-68 (Folder 35)
    - Jessup, John C., 1964 (Folder 36)
    - Kilgour, David E., 1964 (Folder 37)
    - Kilpatrick, Evron M., 1964 (Folder 38)
    - Kruger, Horst, 1964 (Folder 39)
    - Larmon, Sigurd, 1964 (Folder 40)
    - Layton, Christopher, 1964-65 (Folder 41)
    - Lerner, Max, 1964 (Folder 42)
    - Lipson, Leslie, 1965-69 (Folder 42A)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1961-65 (322, Folder 1)
    - Lord, Mary, 1965 (Folder 2)
    - McCloy, John J., 1967 (Folder 3)
    - McElroy, Neil, 1964 (Folder 4)
    - MacMillan, H. R., 1963-67 (Folder 5)
    - McQuade, Lawrence C., 1964 (Folder 6)
    - Mally, Gerhard, 1964-68 (Folder 7)
    - Marc, Alexandre, 1963-69 (Folder 8)
    - Mathews, John A., 1963-64 (Folder 9)
    - Merchant, Livingston T., 1967-68 (Folder 10)
    - Moore, Ben T., 1964-66 (Folder 11)
    - Moore, Walden, 1963-65 (Folder 12)
    - Morgan, George A., 1964 (Folder 13)
    - Murden, Forrest D., 1964 (Folder 14)
    - Nellen, Eugene, 1969-1970 (Folder 15)
    - Nere, Jacques, 1965 (Folder 16)
    - Neumann, Robert G., 1963-66 (Folder 17)
    - Nichols, Calvin J., 1964 (Folder 18)
    - Norstad, Lauris, 1964-65 (Folder 19)
    - Oppenheim, Friedrich C., von, 1964-65 (Folder 20)
    - Osgood, Robert E., 1964 (Folder 21)
    - Pallay, E. S., 1964-65 (Folder 22)
    - Phillips, Joseph
      - 1965-66 (Folder 23)
      - 1967-68 (Folder 24)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1964-65 (Folder 25)
    - Reifenberg, Jan G., 1965-67 (323, Folder 1)
    - Reinstein, Jacques J., 1964-65 (Folder 2)
    - Ritchie, Ronald S., 1965 (Folder 3)
    - Rittberger, Volker, 1969 (Folder 4)
    - Robertson, Ian, 1964-65 (Folder 5)
    - Rohde, Howard, 1964 (Folder 6)
    - Rostow, Eugene, 1964-67 (Folder 7)
    - Ryan, Charles
      - 1963 (Folder 8)
      - 1963-64 (Folder 9)
      - 1965 (Folder 10)
      - 1966-67 (Folder 11)
    - Safran, William, 1967 (Folder 12)
    - Scelba, Cipriana, 1969 (Folder 13)
    - Schaetzel, J. Robert, 1962-67 (Folder 14)
    - Schmidt, Adolf, 1963-68 (Folder 15)
    - Slater, Joseph E., 1964 (Folder 16)
    - Stahl, Walter, 1964-65 (Folder 17)
    - Stillman, Richard J., 1965 (Folder 18)
    - Stanford University, 1963-67 (Folder 19)
    - Stout, Richard, 1964 (Folder 20)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1964-68 (Folder 21)
    - Szent-Miklosy, Istvan, 1963-68 (Folder 22)
    - Taylor, Mrs. Paul, 1966 (Folder 23)
    - Uri, Pierre, 1964-67 (Folder 24)
    - Wallace, Richard, 1966-68 (Folder 25)
    - Walmsley, Walter N., 1963-65 (324, Folder 1)
    - Wilgress, L. Dana, 1964-65 (Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Carroll, 1974 (Folder 3)
  - Debt servicing meeting, March 1, 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Deposit slips
    - 1963 (Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Folder 6)
  - Dowling, Walter C.
    - Correspondence
      - 1963-64 (Folder 7)
      - 1965 (Folder 8)
      - 1966-68 (Folder 9)
    - Trip, (New York), April 1965 (Folder 10)
  - Duroselle, J. B.
    - "The Future of the Atlantic Community,", 1966 (Folder 11)
    - Notes on the French university system, November 1964 (Folder 12)
  - Economic Committee meetings
    - 1971
      - September 25 (Folder 13-14)
      - December 10 (Folder 15)
    - 1972 December (Folder 16)
    - 1972 December (325, Folder 1)
  - Equipment inventory and rental (Folder 2)
  - "Europe and America at the Crossroads,", 1972 (Folder 3)
  - European Agriculture Study
    - Correspondence, 1970-71 (Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (Folder 5)
    - Press conference (Folder 6)
  - Evidence of effectiveness (Folder 7)
  - Expenses
    - 1961-62 (Folder 8)
    - 1963 (Folder 9-10)
    - 1964-65 (Folder 11)
    - 1969 (Folder 12)
  - Expenses/Disbursements, 1968 (Folder 13)
  - Expenses/Disbursements, 1968 (326, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Bulletin, 1966-67 (Folder 2)
  - Finances
    - 1966-67 (Folder 3)
    - 1972 (Folder 4)
  - Financial Report, December 1, 1962 (Folder 5)
  - Fontaine, Francois
    - General (Folder 6)
    - "Draft Program for Atlantic Studies,", 1967 (Folder 7)
  - Foreign Area Fellowship Program (Folder 8)
  - Formation of Atlantic Institute
    - By-laws and historical summary (Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1960
      - January-July (Folder 10)
      - August-September (Folder 11)
      - October-December (327, Folder 1)
  - Foundations (Folder 2-3)
  - "The Free World's Aims for Humanity,", 1962 (Folder 4)
  - Freymond, Jacques (Folder 5)
  - Fundraising
    - General (Folder 6)
    - NASA (Folder 7)
  - "The Future of the Mediterranean" (Folder 8)
  - "The Future of NATO,", 1966 (Folder 9)
  - Gasteyger, Curt, trip, April 17, 1972 (Folder 10)
  - Geneva Conference, May 29-June 1, 1966
    - General (Folder 11)
    - General (328, Folder 1)
    - Follow-up information (Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings (Folder 3)
    - Planning for the, 1970s (Folder 4)
  - German sponsors (possible) (Folder 5)
  - Grant requests
    - 1965 (Folder 6)
    - 1967 (Folder 7)
  - Harned, Joseph W.
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence
      - 1964-67 (Folder 9)
      - 1970 (Folder 10)
    - Trips
      - 1971
        - California (Folder 11)
        - March (Japan) (Folder 12)
        - March (Japan) (329, Folder 1-2)
        - November (Folder 3-4)
      - 1973
        - Moscow (Folder 5)
        - Paris (Folder 6)
        - San Francisco (Folder 7)
      - (Paris), 1976 March (Folder 8)
  - Huntley, James R.
    - Correspondence
      - 1963 (Folder 9)
      - 1963-65 (330, Folder 1)
      - 1965-67 (Folder 2)
    - Expense accounts, 1963 (Folder 3)
    - Expense accounts and travel (Folder 4)
  - Index to United States file (Folder 5)
  - International Communication Project (Folder 6)
  - International Publications Service (Folder 7)
  - Jacobson, Alfred (Folder 8)
  - Japan Foundation (Folder 9)
  - Knoppers, Antonie T.
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Lecture, May 30, 1966 (Folder 11)
    - "The Role of Science and Technology in Atlantic Econo- mic Relationships,", 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Kristensen, Mr., lecture, May 29, 1966 (Folder 13)
  - Lambert, Mr., lecture, May 30, 1966 (Folder 14)
  - Latin America - A Broader World Role, 1973 (Folder 15-16)
  - Latin America Project
    - General (Folder 17)
    - Agriculture and population projects (331, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1970-71 (Folder 2)
    - Subprojects (Folder 3)
  - Lattman, Walter (Folder 4)
  - Library (Folder 5)
  - McCurdy, Carolyn (Folder 6)
  - Martin, William M., speech, May 31, 1966 (Folder 7)
  - Maudling, Reginald, lecture, May 30, 1966 (Folder 8)
  - Meetings
    - 1972 December 1-2 (Folder 9)
    - 1974 June (Folder 10-11)
  - Membership and statutes (Folder 12)
  - Middle East Project, 1974-76
    - General (Folder 13)
    - General (332, Folder 1-3)
    - Funds (Folder 4)
    - Planning Committee (Folder 5)
    - Proposal (Folder 6)
    - Study Groups (Folder 7)
    - Study Groups (333, Folder 1)
    - West European Study Group (Folder 2)
  - Monthly reports
    - 1968 (Folder 3)
    - 1969 (Folder 4)
  - Morse, David, lecture, May 31, 1966 (Folder 5)
  - Multinational enterprises, proposed study of (Folder 6)
  - Murphy Commission
    - Correspondence (Folder 7)
    - Final report, October 31, 1974 (Folder 8)
    - First memorandum, September 23, 1974 (Folder 9)
    - Interviews
      - France (Folder 10)
      - Germany (Folder 11)
      - Great Britain (Folder 12)
    - Paris, memoranda from (Folder 13-14)
    - Proposal (Folder 15)
    - Special projects
      - Correspondence (334, Folder 1)
      - Wittenberg, Ernest, Associates (Folder 2)
    - Support papers (Folder 3-5)
  - NATO Project, 1963-64 (Folder 6-8)
  - NATO Project, 1963-64 (335, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, November 1964 (Folder 2)
  - Norstad, General, lecture, May 30, 1966 (Folder 3)
  - Officers, 1967-1973 (Folder 4)
  - Organizing Committee (Folder 5)
  - Papers and studies
    - Foch, Rene, "L'Europe et la Technologie: Un Point de Vue Politique" (Folder 6)
    - Martin, Lawrence W., "Ballistic Missile Defence and the Alliance,", 1969 (Folder 7)
    - Pearson, Lester B., "Partners in Development,", 1969 (Folder 8)
    - Requests for (Folder 9)
  - Paris
    - 1965 (Folder 10)
    - 1968 (Folder 11)
    - 1969 (336, Folder 1-2)
    - Meetings, 1960
      - October 29 (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - Monthly reports, 1964 (Folder 5)
    - Quarterly reports, 1964 (Folder 6)
  - Partnership for Progress
    - Mailing lists (Folder 7)
    - Promotional file (Folder 8)
  - Peccei, Aurelio
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Lecture, May 30, 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Policy Committee
    - 1961-66 (Folder 11)
    - 1967-68 (Folder 12)
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1962-63 (Folder 14)
  - Prebisch, Raul, speech, May 30, 1966 (337, Folder 1)
  - Program, 1970-71 (Folder 2)
  - Program for Encouraging Atlantic Studies, 1963-64 (Folder 3)
  - Progress reports
    - 1962 July (Folder 4)
    - 1963 (Folder 5)
  - Project: A European Defence Grouping Within NATO, 1968 (Folder 6)
  - Proposed study projects, 1968-69 (Folder 7)
  - Publications
    - Book orders
      - 1971 (Folder 8)
      - 1972 (Folder 9)
    - Complimentary distribution (Folder 10)
    - Distributors (Folder 11)
    - Dunellen flyers, bound volumes, Atlantic Papers Annuals (Folder 12)
    - Lists (Folder 13)
  - Report, 1971 (Folder 14)
  - Report of Current Activities and Plans for, 1971, September 1970 (Folder 15)
  - Report of 1969 Activities and Plans for, 1970, March 1970 (Folder 16)
  - "The Role of Great Britain in Atlantic Economic Relationships,", n.d. (Folder 17)
  - Seminar on Aid to Education in Less-Developed Countries, Bellagio, July 11-19, 1962 (338, Folder 1)
  - Seminars
    - Economic Problems of the Atlantic Community, November-December 1969 (Folder 2)
    - The Future of the Atlantic Community, March 1969 (Folder 3)
    - Trade and investment, 1970-71 (Folder 4)
  - Spaak, Paul Henri, speech, June 1, 1966 (Folder 5)
  - Special projects
    - "Europe and Mediterranean Africa,", October 1971 (Folder 6)
    - International Conference on Trade and Investment Policies, Tokyo, March 25-26, 1971
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Conference papers (Folder 8-9)
    - Research institutes meeting, May 4, 1970 (Folder 10)
    - Tokyo Conference on Energy, October 29-31, 1973
      - Conference (Folder 11-12)
      - Participants, program, working papers (Folder 13)
      - Participants, program, working papers (339, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee for Trade and Investment (Folder 2)
  - Summary Report of Activities, January-April 1969 (Folder 3)
  - Tatu, Michel, "The Great Power Triangle: Washington-Moscow-Peking" (Folder 4)
  - Taxes, 1965-1974 (Folder 5-7)
  - Taylor, Paul B.
    - Correspondence, 1965-66 (Folder 8)
    - Expenses and travel, 1965-66 (Folder 9)
    - German correspondence and addresses, 1965-66 (Folder 10)
  - Technological development (Folder 11)
  - Trade union seminar, 1971 (Folder 12)
  - Treasurer's Report, (3rd quarter), 1964 (Folder 13)
  - Triffin, Robert (Folder 14)
  - Tuthill, John W.
    - 1970 (340, Folder 1-2)
    - 1973 (Folder 3)
    - 1974 (Folder 4)
    - 1975 (Folder 5)
    - "The American Ambassador,", 1974 (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - 1969 (Folder 7-8)
      - 1970 (Folder 9)
    - Speech, (Chapel Hill), October 1970 (Folder 10)
    - "Trade With the Developing Countries,", May 19, 1970 (Folder 11)
    - Trips
      - 1970 May 19-21 (341, Folder 1)
      - 1971
        - March (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - Fall (Folder 4-5)
        - November-December (Folder 6-7)
      - 1972
        - January (Folder 8)
        - Fall (Folder 9-10)
        - December (Washington) (342, Folder 1)
      - 1973 June (Folder 2)
      - 1974
        - March (Folder 3)
        - July (Washington) (Folder 4)
        - October (Folder 5)
      - 1975
        - January (Washington) (Folder 6)
        - March (New York and Washington) (Folder 7)
        - May (Washington) (Folder 8)
        - November (New York and Washington) (Folder 9)
      - 1976
        - March (Washington) (Folder 10)
        - (USA), May-June (Folder 11)
        - July (Folder 12)
        - October (Folder 13)
  - Washington, monthly reports, 1964 (Folder 14)
  - Washington, D. C., 1965 (Folder 15)
  - Washington, D. C., office projects, 1965 (343, Folder 1-2)
  - Young Labor Leaders Program (Folder 3-4)
  - Young Leaders
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Conferences
      - (Copenhagen), 1971 May (Folder 6)
      - 1972 October (Folder 7)
      - 1973 June-July (Folder 8)
    - Meetings
      - (Agricultural policy), 1970 September (Folder 9)
      - 1973 November 29-December 1 (Folder 10)
      - 1974
        - June 11-12 (344, Folder 1)
        - October 10-12 (Folder 2)
      - 1975 (Folder 3)
      - 1976 (Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 5-6)
- ATLANTIC TREATY ASSOCIATION, 1965-1983
  - 1964 (344, Folder 7)
  - 1965 (Folder 8-11)
  - 1966 (345, Folder 1)
  - 1967 (Folder 2)
  - 1967-68 (Folder 3)
  - 1968 (Folder 4)
  - 1969 (Folder 5-8)
  - 1969 (346, Folder 1)
  - 1970 (Folder 2)
  - 1971-72 (Folder 3)
  - 1972 (Folder 4)
  - 1973 (Folder 5-6)
  - 1973-74 (Folder 7)
  - 1974-77 (Folder 8)
  - 1975 (Folder 9)
  - 1976 (347, Folder 1)
  - 1976-77 (Folder 2)
  - 1977 (Folder 3)
  - 1977-78 (Folder 4)
  - 1978 (Folder 5-6)
  - 1979 (Folder 7-9)
  - 1979-1980 (Folder 10)
  - 1981-83 (348, Folder 1)
  - Ambassadors and embassies (Folder 2)
  - "The Atlantic Citizen: An Account of the Work of the Atlantic Treaty Asociation,", May 1975 (Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Institute joint meetings
    - 1962 December 1 (Folder 4)
    - (Brussels), 1963 May 28-June 8 (Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Mail (Courrier Atlantique)
    - 1963 (Folder 6-7)
    - 1963-64 (Folder 8)
    - 1964 (Folder 9)
  - Beyond Diplomacy (Folder 10)
  - Bills (Folder 11)
  - Bonn Conference, March 1963 (Folder 12)
  - Brussels (Folder 13)
  - Brussels Council, February 1978 (349, Folder 1)
  - Brussels seminar, February 1977 (Folder 2)
  - Committee on the Challenges of Modern Society (Folder 3)
  - Committee on Environment, meeting, September 22, 1970 (Folder 4)
  - Committees, 1974-75 (Folder 5)
  - Conference, October 20-24, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Conference planning, 1969 (Folder 7)
  - Constitution, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Contributions from ACUS, 1974-75 (Folder 9)
  - Correspondence
    - 1962-63 (Folder 10)
    - 1964 (Folder 11)
  - Council meetings
    - 1961
      - January 12-13 (Folder 12)
      - September 24-29 (Folder 13)